exidelife.in 2019-12-17

# Exide Life Insurance - Privacy Policy

### Information

The User specifically acknowledges that any communication transmitted by them to Exide Life Insurance Company Limited (here in after referred to as "Exide Life")via the Internet may not be secure from interference or remain confidential during its transmission. Exide Life may be required to disclose information pursuant to applicable law, rule, regulation or such other requirements as may be in force from time to time.

Exide Life Insurance undertakes not to disclose, except as otherwise provided, the Personal Information provided by You to any person, unless such action is necessary to: 

  * - Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process
  * - Protect and defend Exide Lifes or its Affiliates rights, interests or property
  * - Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services or Terms and Conditions; or
  * - Act to protect the interests of Exide Life, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons

Except as otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying, redistribution, re-transmission, publication or commercial exploitation of material will be permitted without our express permission or that of the copyright owner. In the event of any permitted copying, redistribution or publication of copyright material, no changes in or deletion of author attribution, trademark legend or copyright notice shall be made.

### Use Of Information

The User of this website specifically acknowledges and agrees that Exide Life will not be liable for any illegal and/or slanderous conduct of any person. Exide Life's website sometimes requires Users to give personal information in order to do things like access webcasts, download documents, participate in online surveys, or to provide feedback. In situations like these, where Users are accessing the website, Exide Life recognizes Users interest in the product or service and considers that to be "opting in"to allow Exide Life and appropriate business partners of Exide Life to contact Users with information, special offers, or promotional materials in the future. Exide Life may transfer Users personal information to or share it with the business partner only for future marketing, development of new products, customer service, delivery of products, aftercare service and related activities thereof. If the User does not wish to be contacted, the User is requested to intimate Exide Life accordingly.

Exide Life may also collect information in other ways, such as running quizzes, contests or any other program on Exide Life's site or otherwise, in which Exide Life will ask the User for contact information (like postal and email address), unique identifiers (like password), and demographic information (like occupation). If User does not wish to be contacted, Exide Life requests that the User does not participate in these promotions.

Exide Life may share the information provided by the User with any other person(s) including its affiliates, business partners, re-insurers, and other third parties such as service providers. In addition, should the law or an authority require to do so, Exide Life may disclose any information provided by the User in the website, as required. Further, Exide Life will release personal information to (i) enforce or apply Exide Life agreements, (ii) protect Exide Life rights and property; and (iii) protect integrity or safety of Exide Life and this site.

 It is specifically agreed that Exide Life shall be entitled to compile and analyze such information on an aggregated basis for its purposes. In pursuance of the same, Exide Life shall be entitled to prepare from such information such documentation, graphs or figures that it may think necessary for its purposes which may include, among others, preparation of feasibility studies, marketing or distribution methods and processes, customer lists, current and anticipated privacy requirements, commission structure, market studies, business plans, financial projections and budgets, projected profits, names and backgrounds of personnel and personnel training techniques and materials.

### Links

This site may contain links to other sites. Exide Life does not control the information collection of sites that can be reached through links from this or any site controlled by Exide Life. If the User has questions about the data collection procedures or privacy policy of linked sites, please contact those sites directly. Exide Life does not undertake any responsibility for the privacy policies of the Internet service providers, partners, advertisers, and web sites that have links on this website that may collect personally identifiable information of any form from the User while accessing this or those sites through this website.
